A Guide to the Records of the Office of the Dean of Virginia Tech Carilion School of Medicine, Cynda Ann Johnson, 2008-2018
Special Collections and University Archives, Virginia Tech
- Series I: Subject Files
  - Advisory Board Meeting, 2008-07-16 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Meeting to Constitute Official Board of VTC, 2008-08-15 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - VTC Board Meeting, 2008-09-24 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - VTCSOM Executive Committee Minutes (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - VTCSOM Board Meeting, 2008-10-22 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - VTCSOM Board Meeting, Terri Workman's Copy, 2008-11-19 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - VTCSOM Board Meeting, 2008-11-19 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - VTCSOM Board Meeting, 2008-12-03 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - School of Medicine Board Meetings, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - School of Medicine Board Meeting Minutes, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - VTCSOM Board Meeting, 2009-01-28 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - VTCSOM Board Meeting, 2009-03-25 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - VTCSOM Board Meeting, Terri Workman's Copy, 2009-05-27 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - VTCSOM Board Meeting, 2009-05-27 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - VTCSOM Board Meeting, 2009-06-24 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - VTCSOM Board Meeting, Terri Workman's Copy, 2009-06-24 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - VTCSOM Annual Report, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - VTCSOM Board Meeting, Terri Workman's Copy, 2009-08-26 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - VTCSOM Board Meeting, 2009-08-26 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - VTCSOM Board Meeting, Terri Workman's Copy, 2009-09-23 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - VTCSOM Board Meeting, 2009-09-23 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - VTCSOM Board Meeting, 2009-10-28 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - VTCSOM Board Meeting, Terri Workman's Copy, 2009-10-28 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - School of Medicine Board Meetings, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - School of Medicine Board Meeting Minutes, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Board Working Papers, Terri Workman's Copy, 2010-01-26 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - VTCSOM Board Meeting, 2010-01-27 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - VTC Board Meeting Working Papers, Terri Workman's Copy, 2010-02 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - VTCSOM Board Meeting, 2010-02-24 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - VTCSOM Board Meeting, Restricted Data Removed, 2010-02-24 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - VTCSOM Board Meeting, Terri Workman's Copy, 2010-04-28 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - VTCSOM Board Meeting, 2010-04-28 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - VTCSOM Board Meeting, 2010-05-26 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - VTCSOM Board Meeting, Terri Workman's Copy, 2010-05-26 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - VTCSOM Board Meeting, 2010-06-23 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - VTCSOM Board Meeting, Terri Workman's Copy, 2010-06-23 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - VTCSOM Board Meeting, 2010-07-27 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - VTCSOM Board Meeting, 2010-08-25 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Drafts for August Board, Terri Workman's Copy, 2010 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Sept. Board, Terri Workman's Copy, 2010 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - VTCSOM Board Meeting, 2010-09-22 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - VTCSOM Board Meeting, Terri Workman's Copy, 2010-09-22 (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - VTCSOM Board Meeting, 2010-10-27 (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - VTCSOM Board Meeting, 2010-12-08 (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - School of Medicine Board Meetings, 2010 (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - School of Medicine Board Meeting Minutes, 2010 (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - VTCSOM Board Meeting, 2011-01-26 (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - VTCSOM Called Board Meeting, 2011-02-11 (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - VTCSOM Board Meeting, 2011-02-23 (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - Substantive Change Policy (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - VTCSOM Board Meeting, 2011-03-23 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - VTCSOM Board Meeting, 2011-04-27 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - VTCSOM Board Meeting, 2011-05-25 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - School of Medicine Board Meeting Minutes, 2011 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - VTCSOM Board Meeting, 2011-06-22 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - VTCSOM Board Meeting, 2011-07-27 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - VTCSOM Board Meeting, 2011-10-28 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - VTCSOM Board Meeting, 2013-04-01 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - VTC Board of Directors Meeting, 2013-09-30 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - School of Medicine Board Meetings, 2013 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - VTCSOM Board Meeting, 2014-03-19 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - VTCSOM Board Meeting, 2014-06-25 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - VTCSOM Board Meeting, 2014-09-30 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - VTCSOM Board Meeting, 2014-12-09 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Cynda - Board Review Flash Drive [RESTRICTED] (Box 19)
- Series II: Publications
  - Published Newsletters/Magazines, 2004-2009 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Published Newsletter/Magazines, 2010-2015 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Levitov Chapter 20: Education and Training in Portable Bedside Ultrasound: The Life Cycle of the Clinician (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Carilion Clinic Calendar, 2009 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - University of Kansas Medical Center Dept. of Family Medicine Annual Report, 2013-2014 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Transforming Patient Care: Aligning Interprofessional Education with Clinical Practice Redesign by Josiah Macy Jr. Foundation, 2013-06 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - The Wonder of a Woman, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Series III: Plaques
  - National Family Medicine Interest Group Network Plaque for Program of Excellence Award Presented to VTCSOM Family Medicine Interest Group, 2015-2016 (Box 18)
  - Carilion Clinic Proclamation - International Clean Hands Week 2010: "Clean Hands Save Lives" (Box 18)
- Series IV: Personal Items
  - "Meet Me In Kansas" Pool Party and BBQ Invitations (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Johnson Scrapbook (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Brody School of Medicine Dean Appointment Announcement (Box 18, Folder 6)